const questions = [
  {
    question: "In 1986, this arcade game, known for its difficulty, featured a ninja on a mission to rescue Irene Lew. What is the title of this challenging game?",
    choices: ["Shinobi", "The Legend of Kage", "Ninja Gaiden", "Strider"],
    correctAnswer: "Ninja Gaiden"
  },
  {
    question: "True or False: The 1987 action RPG 'Ys: Ancient Ys Vanished' follows the adventures of Adol Christin as he explores the mysterious land of Esteria.",
    choices: ["TRUE", "FALSE"],
    correctAnswer: "TRUE"
  },
  {
    question: "Which 1988 puzzle-platformer, known for its intricate level design and cryptic puzzles, features a character named Lester Knight Chaykin? Choose the correct title.",
    choices: ["Flashback", "Prince of Persia", "Another World", "Heart of the Alien"],
    correctAnswer: "Another World"
  },
  {
    question: "True or False: The 1985 strategy game 'Little Sim People' allows players to interact with virtual inhabitants living inside a computer-generated house.",
    choices: ["TRUE", "FALSE"],
    correctAnswer: "FALSE"
  },
  {
    question: "This 1982 arcade game, featuring a spaceship battling waves of aliens, is often considered one of the first shoot 'em ups. What is its title?",
    choices: ["Defender", "Phoenix", "Centipede", "Galaxian"],
    correctAnswer: "Galaxian"
  },
  {
    question: "In 1989, a platformer called 'Prince of Persia' was released, known for its rotoscoped animation and realistic movements. True or False?",
    choices: ["TRUE", "FALSE"],
    correctAnswer: "TRUE"
  },
  {
    question: "Which 1983 maze arcade game, designed by Warren Davis and Jeff Lee? Choose the correct title.",
    choices: ["BurgerTime", "Q*bert", "Dig Dug", "Mr. Do!"],
    correctAnswer: "Q*bert"
  },
  {
    question: "True or False: 'Ghostbusters: The Video Game' released in 1984, is a FPS where players take on the role of a Ghostbuster.",
    choices: ["TRUE", "FALSE"],
    correctAnswer: "FALSE"
  },
  {
    question: "In 1981, a scrolling shooter game featuring the Vic Viper spacecraft was released. What is the title of this classic shoot 'em up game?",
    choices: ["Gradius", "Raiden", "Zaxxon", "Scramble"],
    correctAnswer: "Gradius"
  },
  {
    question: "True or False: 'Wizardry: Proving Grounds of the Mad Overlord,' released in 1981, is often considered one of the earliest examples of a computer role-playing game.",
    choices: ["TRUE", "FALSE"],
    correctAnswer: "TRUE"
  }
];

questions.sort(() => Math.random() - 0.5);

//This page was the easiest to build as it is a questions page.
